<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Default -->
    <string name="app_name">Rayvue</string>
    <string name="error_title">Error</string>
    <string name="warning_title">Warning!</string>
    <string name="question_title">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="action_positive_title">OK</string>
    <string name="action_negative_title">Cancel</string>

    <!-- Main -->
    <string name="nav_games_title">Games</string>
    <string name="nav_awards_title">Awards</string>
    <string name="nav_journal_title">Journal</string>

    <!-- Account Screen -->
    <string name="account_prompt_message">Create a free account to save your data in the cloud.</string>
    <string name="account_button_login_title">Log in</string>
    <string name="account_button_signup_title">Sign up</string>
    <string name="account_button_no_account_title">Continue with no account</string>

    <!-- Login Screen -->
    <string name="login_prompt_message">Log in with your email and password.</string>
    <string name="login_send_data_error_message">An error occurred while trying to log in.</string>
    <string name="login_email_hint">Your email</string>
    <string name="login_email_support">You\'ll have to remember it</string>
    <string name="login_email_error">The account with this email doesn\'t exist</string>
    <string name="login_password_hint">Your password</string>
    <string name="login_password_support">You can\'t request a reset at the moment</string>
    <string name="login_password_error">Wrong password</string>
    <string name="login_button_title">Enter account</string>

    <!-- Signup Screen -->
    <string name="signup_prompt_message">Sign up with an email and a password.</string>
    <string name="signup_validate_data_error_message">An error occurred while trying to verify if this account already exists.</string>
    <string name="signup_email_hint">Email</string>
    <string name="signup_email_support">The email has to be correct and complete</string>
    <string name="signup_email_error">Email is linked to an existing account</string>
    <string name="signup_password_hint">Password</string>
    <string name="signup_password_support">Minimum 10 characters including 1 uppercase and 1 digit</string>
    <string name="signup_button_title">Next</string>

    <!-- Input Name Screen -->
    <string name="input_name_prompt_message">Add your name or choose an username.</string>
    <string name="input_name_name_hint">Name</string>
    <string name="input_name_name_support">Maximum 20 characters</string>
    <string name="input_name_button_title">Sign up</string>
    <string name="input_name_send_signup_data_error_message">An error occurred while trying to sign up.</string>

    <!-- Games Screen -->
    <string name="games_get_data_error_message">An error occurred. Check your Internet connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="games_section_recent_title">Recently Added</string>
    <string name="games_section_discover_title">Discover</string>
    <string name="games_section_all_title">All Games</string>

    <!-- Awards Screen -->
    <string name="awards_get_data_error_message">No games with this award were found.</string>
    <string name="awards_tab_week_title">Week</string>
    <string name="awards_tab_month_title">Month</string>
    <string name="awards_tab_year_title">Year</string>
    <string name="awards_section_past_title">Past Awards</string>

    <!-- Journal Screen -->
    <string name="journal_get_data_error_message">You haven\'t added any games to your journal.</string>

    <!-- Entry Screen -->
    <string name="entry_title">Journal</string>
    <string name="entry_select_placeholder">Select a game</string>
    <string name="entry_write_hint">Write something in your journal…</string>
    <string name="entry_button_save_title">Save</string>
    <string name="entry_send_data_error_message">An error occurred. The entry could not be uploaded to the server. It was saved only locally instead.</string>
    <string name="entry_send_data_success_message">The entry was successfully saved.</string>
    <string name="entry_replace_confirm_message">You\'ve already created a journal entry for this game. Do you want to replace its data?</string>

    <!-- Search Screen -->
    <string name="search_general_placeholder">Enter your search</string>
    <string name="search_database_placeholder">Search all games</string>
    <string name="search_local_placeholder">Search your games</string>

    <!-- Game Details Screen -->
    <string name="game_details_get_data_error_message">An error occurred. Details for this game could not be loaded.</string>
    <string name="game_details_empty_data_error_message">No reviews have been found for this game. Add one yourself.</string>
    <string name="game_details_section_reviews_title">Reviews</string>
    <string name="game_details_section_categories_title">Categories</string>
    <string name="game_details_section_keep_in_mind_title">Keep In Mind</string>
    <string name="game_details_tag_price_symbol">\$%1$s</string>
    <string name="game_details_tag_price_free">Free</string>
    <string name="game_details_tag_sub_message">Subscription service</string>
    <string name="game_details_tag_micro_message">Micro-transactions</string>
    <string name="game_details_tag_pass_message">Battle pass</string>
    <string name="game_details_tag_loot_message">Loot boxes</string>
    <string name="game_details_tag_p2w_message">Pay-to-win</string>
    <string name="game_details_tag_malicious_message">Malicious practices</string>
    <string name="game_details_tag_tos_message">Concerning TOS</string>
    <string name="game_details_tag_fake_message">Fake engagement</string>
    <string name="game_details_tag_ad_message">Not as advertised</string>
    <string name="game_details_tag_dev_message">Immoral developers</string>
    <string name="game_details_tag_scam_message">Scam</string>

    <!-- Reviews Screen -->
    <string name="reviews_get_data_error_message">An error occurred. Reviews could not be loaded.</string>
    <string name="reviews_empty_data_error_message">No reviews have been found.</string>
    <string name="reviews_send_data_error_message">An error occurred. The review could not be posted.</string>
    <string name="reviews_write_hint">Write a review</string>
    <string name="reviews_info_no_account">You need an account to leave a review.</string>
    <string name="reviews_info_review_exists">You\'ve already added a review for this game.</string>
    <string name="reviews_info_not_accredited">You are not allowed to review games.</string>

    <!-- Tags Info Screen -->
    <string name="tags_info_title">Keep In Mind</string>
    <string name="tags_info_sub_title">What is a subscription service?</string>
    <string name="tags_info_sub_meaning">A subscription service is a system where game companies charge a certain amount of money in exchange for users accessing their game every week/month/year or other predetermined period of time.</string>
    <string name="tags_info_micro_title">What are micro-transactions?</string>
    <string name="tags_info_micro_meaning">Micro-transactions are in-game items that the users can purchase using real money. The problem with micro-transactions is that the difficulty of the game is made in such a way that the players cannot progress in a reasonable amount of time without paying for said micro-transactions. Another problem is that those in-game items are created in such a way that if the players want to keep winning, they will have to keep buying them endlessly, potentially spending thousands of dollars (or any other real-life currency).</string>
    <string name="tags_info_pass_title">What is a battle pass?</string>
    <string name="tags_info_pass_meaning">A battle pass is a subscription service for the potential to win in-game items. It is usually split into a basic battle pass (free) and a premium battle pass, with the premium version offering better rewards than the basic one. All battle passes are designed in such a way that the player has to keep playing the game to get better and better rewards, making it addictive in the process.</string>
    <string name="tags_info_loot_title">What are loot boxes?</string>
    <string name="tags_info_loot_meaning">Loot boxes are micro-transactions that contain different prizes which can only be obtained randomly, similar to gambling. The worst aspects of those boxes is that sometimes the player can get absolutely nothing, the rewards are usually useless and the best prizes can only be obtained if the player opens hundreds or even thousands of such boxes. Loot boxes, of course, can be divided into boxes with potentially useful prizes and boxes with fairly useless prizes.</string>
    <string name="tags_info_p2w_title">What is pay-to-win?</string>
    <string name="tags_info_p2w_meaning">Pay-to-win is the name of a type of game that implements practices designed to make the user spend exorbitant amounts of money for a chance to win. Not all games that implement micro-transactions are necessarily pay-to-win, as useful prizes can usually be obtained just by playing, without the need to spend real money. However, in cases where it is clear that a game cannot be completed or even played without the user spending money on loot boxes, battle passes or other micro-transactions, it is marked as pay-to-win.</string>
    <string name="tags_info_malicious_title">What are malicious practices?</string>
    <string name="tags_info_malicious_meaning">Other malicious practices are hidden psychological tricks added to make players spend more money without realizing it. Such tricks may include creating more in-game coins so that the user does not think twice when spending them, with the main purpose being to dilute the value of real money.</string>
    <string name="tags_info_tos_title">What are concerning TOS?</string>
    <string name="tags_info_tos_meaning">Concerning Terms of Service are crafted in such a way that it legally allows the company that owns the game to screw the user without repercussion, either by stealing all of their data, denying refunds, or even monitoring their device.</string>
    <string name="tags_info_fake_title">What is fake engagement?</string>
    <string name="tags_info_fake_meaning">Fake engagement refers to buying positive reviews for a game. Not on this platform, though.</string>
    <string name="tags_info_ad_title">What does \"not as advertised\" mean?</string>
    <string name="tags_info_ad_meaning">When a game is labeled as such, it means that all promotional art created to advertise the game completely misrepresents the final product. For example: a company releases a trailer (short video that should realistically present the game) that makes it look like their game contains the ability to shoot enemies. In reality, after the users download it, expecting what they saw in the trailer, they find out that it\'s just a generic game of managing a base and its resources, no shooting included.</string>
    <string name="tags_info_dev_title">What are immoral developers?</string>
    <string name="tags_info_dev_meaning">Immoral developers usually lie to their community, for example by making false promises. It could also mean they or the company they work for has allegations or convictions of employee misconduct (for example, workplace harassment).</string>
    <string name="tags_info_scam_title">What is defined as a scam?</string>
    <string name="tags_info_scam_meaning">A game labeled with \"scam\" is a game that was advertised to convince people to buy it, either at launch, by pre-ordering, or by investing money before it was even created, but turned out to be incomplete, with major bugs and generally a total disappointment at launch. A good example would be the following: developers start a campaign to raise funds for the creation of a promised game, but the money obtained is used more for the personal interests of the people behind the campaign (in other words, the money is stolen). When the time comes for the game to be released, it doesn\'t look even remotely similar to what was promised (and what people invested their own money in) because there weren\'t enough funds left to develop that version of the game.</string>

    <!-- Settings Screen -->
    <string name="settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_welcome_account_message">Hello, %1$s!</string>
    <string name="settings_welcome_no_account_message">Hello! You\'re not logged in.</string>
    <string name="settings_get_data_error_message">An error occurred. Your account could not be loaded.</string>
    <string name="settings_category_account_title">Account</string>
    <string name="settings_login_text">Log in</string>
    <string name="settings_login_subtext">Enter your account</string>
    <string name="settings_signup_text">Sign up</string>
    <string name="settings_signup_subtext">Create a new account</string>
    <string name="settings_log_out_text">Log out</string>
    <string name="settings_log_out_subtext">Exit your account</string>
    <string name="settings_log_out_prompt_message">You will need to log back in to leave reviews.</string>
    <string name="settings_log_out_error_message">Could not log out.</string>
    <string name="settings_sign_out_text">Delete account</string>
    <string name="settings_sign_out_subtext">This is a permanent action!</string>
    <string name="settings_sign_out_prompt_message">You cannot undo this! Make sure you clicked on this intentionally.</string>
    <string name="settings_sing_out_error_message">Could not delete account.</string>
    <string name="settings_category_info_title">Info</string>
    <string name="settings_about_reviewer_text">What is a certified reviewer?</string>
    <string name="settings_about_reviewer_subtext">A certified reviewer is a person who has been exclusively invited to leave public reviews on any game.</string>
    <string name="settings_about_invite_text">How do I get certified?</string>
    <string name="settings_about_invite_subtext">Only professional game reviewers can become certified.</string>
    <string name="settings_app_version_text">App version: %1$s</string>

</resources>